export const chapter = "Chapter - 13: Phrases and Clauses ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What is a group of words in a sentence that functions like a noun called?",
          optionA: "Adjective Phrase",
          optionB: "Noun Phrase",
          optionC: "Verb Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "B) Noun Phrase",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which type of phrase consists of a preposition and its object?",
          optionA: "Adverb Phrase",
          optionB: "Noun Phrase",
          optionC: "Prepositional Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "C) Prepositional Phrase",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A group of words in a sentence that functions like an adjective is known as:",
          optionA: "Adverb Phrase",
          optionB: "Adjective Phrase",
          optionC: "Noun Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "B) Adjective Phrase",
        },
        {
          question: "What does a verb phrase contain?",
          optionA: "Only one form of a verb",
          optionB: "Different forms of a verb",
          optionC: "Only helping verbs",
          correctAnswer: "B) Different forms of a verb",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which type of clause is independent and not dependent on any other clause for its meaning?",
          optionA: "Subordinate Clause",
          optionB: "Principal Clause",
          optionC: "Coordinate Clause",
          correctAnswer: "B) Principal Clause",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In a conditional sentence, if the situation is unlikely or impossible, which tense is generally used?",
          optionA: "Present Tense",
          optionB: "Future Tense",
          optionC: "Past Tense",
          correctAnswer: "C) Past Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What type of clause tells about the time, place, reason, purpose, condition, or concession?",
          optionA: "Principal Clause",
          optionB: "Coordinate Clause",
          optionC: "Subordinate Clause",
          correctAnswer: "C) Subordinate Clause",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sequence of tenses, if the Principal Clause is in the Present or Future Tense, the Subordinate Clause will be in which tense?",
          optionA: "Past Tense",
          optionB: "Present or Future Tense",
          optionC: "Present Perfect Tense",
          correctAnswer: "B) Present or Future Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which type of phrase consists of a group of words that functions like an adverb?",
          optionA: "Adjective Phrase",
          optionB: "Adverb Phrase",
          optionC: "Noun Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "B) Adverb Phrase",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the main demand made by the Congress during the Cripps Mission in 1942?",
          optionA: "Immediate withdrawal of British from India",
          optionB: "Acceptance of the two-nation theory",
          optionC: "Creation of Pakistan",
          correctAnswer: "A) Immediate withdrawal of British from India",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which type of sentence comprises a Principal Clause and a Subordinate Clause in a conditional clause?",
          optionA: "Complex Sentence",
          optionB: "Compound Sentence",
          optionC: "Simple Sentence",
          correctAnswer: "A) Complex Sentence",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "A group of words in a sentence that functions like a ________ is called a Noun Phrase.",
          optionA: "Adjective",
          optionB: "Noun",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "B) Noun",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adjective Phrases function like an ________ in a sentence.",
          optionA: "Adjective",
          optionB: "Noun",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "A) Adjective",
        },
        {
          question: "A Verb Phrase contains different forms of ________.",
          optionA: "Noun",
          optionB: "Adjective",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "C) Verb",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverb Phrases function like an ________ in a sentence.",
          optionA: "Adjective",
          optionB: "Noun",
          optionC: "Adverb",
          correctAnswer: "C) Adverb",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A Prepositional Phrase consists of a Preposition and its ________.",
          optionA: "Verb",
          optionB: "Object",
          optionC: "Adjective",
          correctAnswer: "B) Object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In a Subordinate Clause, the meaning is dependent upon the ________ for its full meaning.",
          optionA: "Noun Phrase",
          optionB: "Adjective Phrase",
          optionC: "Principal Clause",
          correctAnswer: "C) Principal Clause",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The declaration of Poorna Swaraj (complete freedom) by the Congress in 1929 happened during the ________ session.",
          optionA: "Swaraj",
          optionB: "Lahore",
          optionC: "Simon",
          correctAnswer: "B) Lahore",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The main demand made by the Congress during the Cripps Mission in 1942 was the immediate withdrawal of ________ from India.",
          optionA: "French",
          optionB: "British",
          optionC: "Dutch",
          correctAnswer: "B) British",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Quit India Movement initiated by the Congress in 1942 was ________ by the British government.",
          optionA: "Supported",
          optionB: "Ignored",
          optionC: "Suppressed",
          correctAnswer: "C) Suppressed",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The last major movement led by the Congress before India gained independence in 1947 was the ________.",
          optionA: "Civil Disobedience Movement",
          optionB: "Quit India Movement",
          optionC: "Simon Commission Protest",
          correctAnswer: "B) Quit India Movement",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "A Noun Phrase is a group of words in a sentence that functions like an adjective.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adjective Phrases always contain a Noun or Pronoun as their main word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "A) True",
        },
        {
          question: "A Verb Phrase contains various forms of a single verb.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverb Phrases can never function as modifiers in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A Prepositional Phrase consists only of a preposition, excluding its object.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A Subordinate Clause is always independent and does not rely on any other clause for its meaning.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Coordinate Clauses express their meanings fully and independently.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "A) True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In a conditional clause, a hypothetical or unreal condition is expressed using Present Tense.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Quit India Movement initiated by the Congress in 1942 gained immediate independence for India.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Communal Award in 1934 reserved 50% seats in Provincial Legislative Councils for untouchables.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "B) False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
